<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Main Dish on Mark Boss</title>
    <link>https://markboss.de/tags/main-dish/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Main Dish on Mark Boss</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2016 14:17:13 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://markboss.de/tags/main-dish/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Mexican lasagne</title>
      <link>https://markboss.de/receipe/maindish/mexican-lasagne/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2016 14:17:13 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://markboss.de/receipe/maindish/mexican-lasagne/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Some might want to call them: Burritos for lazy people. You can’t go wrong with burritos.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://markboss.de/images/mexican-lasagne.jpeg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;ingredients:f08e91c4863216579c1f0e3dfce3a535&#34;&gt;Ingredients&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For 2-3 persons:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;lasagne:f08e91c4863216579c1f0e3dfce3a535&#34;&gt;Lasagne&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;400g small potatoes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;200g mushrooms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 onions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 garlic cloves&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 can of kidney beans&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 can chickpeas&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 can corn&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 cans crushed tomatoes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;300ml vegetable broth&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 tbsp. tomato paste&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sugar, pepper, salt, cumin, oregano, marjoram&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;oil&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;wraps (the big one. I’ve used 3 wraps)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;cheese-topping:f08e91c4863216579c1f0e3dfce3a535&#34;&gt;Cheese topping&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;100g cashews&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 tbsp. tahini&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;lemon juice&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;cooking:f08e91c4863216579c1f0e3dfce3a535&#34;&gt;Cooking&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let the cashews soak in water. Ideally overnight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I like potatoes with skin. So I just washed the potatoes thoroughly. You can peel them if you want. Chop the potatoes in 1 cm cubes, cut the mushshrooms into slices, dice the onion and garlic. Drain the  chickpeas, kidney beans and corn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pick a big, deep pan and roast the potatoes in some oil.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pick a cooking pot and add the onions. When the onions are translucent add the garlic and deglaze with the crushed tomatoes. Add 200ml broth and season with the listed spice to taste. Let everything simmer until thickend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Preheat the stove to 180°C.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When the potatoes are done add the kidney beans, corn, chickpeas, the remaining broth and the tomato paste to the pan. Let everything cook for 5 minutes and add the shrooms. After 2-3 minutes season again and remove the pan from heat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you like your sauce creamy, you can blend the tomato sauce. I skipped this step.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Blend the cashews and add water until the mix has a cream cheese consistency. Add the tahini. Season with the lemon juice and salt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pick a baking dish, add some tomato sauce and top with a wrap. You may need to cut the wrap to fit the dish. Add another layer of tomato sauce and top with the filling. Add another layer of tomato sauce and continue until the baking dish is filled. The last layer should be a wrap layer with some tomato sauce on top. Add the cheese topping. You can create a nice grid pattern.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bake everything for 25-30 minutes in the stove. Enjoy your meal.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eggplant in tomato sauce with a parsley dip and Djuvec rice</title>
      <link>https://markboss.de/receipe/maindish/eggplant-tomato-sauce-djuvec-rice/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2016 20:34:06 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://markboss.de/receipe/maindish/eggplant-tomato-sauce-djuvec-rice/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;I really love roasted eggplant. I guess it&amp;rsquo;s started with some falafel food places where you can add roasted eggplant to the falafel. With the parsley dip it&amp;rsquo;s a great summer dish.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://markboss.de/images/eggplant-tomato-sauce-djuvec-rice.jpeg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;ingredients:5db2b51be7942a0dbb57ff139c8fb4d3&#34;&gt;Ingredients&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For 3-4 Persons:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;eggplants-in-tomato-sauce:5db2b51be7942a0dbb57ff139c8fb4d3&#34;&gt;Eggplants in tomato sauce&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3 eggplant&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 can of crushed tomatoes (400ml)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3 garlic cloves&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;turmeric, cayenne pepper, sugar, salt and pepper&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;parsley-dip:5db2b51be7942a0dbb57ff139c8fb4d3&#34;&gt;Parsley dip&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;250g soy yoghurt&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;lots of parsley&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;salt and pepper&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;djuvec-rice:5db2b51be7942a0dbb57ff139c8fb4d3&#34;&gt;Djuvec rice&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 onion&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 garlic cloves&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;300g rice&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 can of crushed tomatoes (400ml)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;500ml vegetable broth&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3 tbsp ajvar&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 red pepper&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;200g peas&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;oil&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;paprika, salt, lots of pepper&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;cooking:5db2b51be7942a0dbb57ff139c8fb4d3&#34;&gt;Cooking&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So we start with slicing the eggplant in slices (approx 1cm thick) and salt them from both sides. Let them sit for 5 minutes. In the meantime dice your onions, red pepper and finely dice the garlic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Heat some oil in a pot and add the onions. Simultaneously heat some oil in a pan and start roasting the eggplants in small portions. Roast each side for approx 4 minutes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When the onions are translucent add the garlic and let them simmer a bit. Afterwards add the broth, tomatoes, ajvar and rice. Season with the listed spices to taste. Add the red pepper and peas. Cook for 25 minutes and stir occasionally.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When all eggplant slices are done, let the remaining garlic simmer for a bit. Add the crushed tomatoes, eggplants and season with the listed spices. Heat everything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While waiting for the rice and eggplants just add a huge amount of parsley to the soy yoghurt and season to taste.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That&amp;rsquo;s it. Enjoy your meal.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>